(Sheldon:)Right. Always right.
(Howard:)He's a righty.
(Penny:)Okay,
(Barry:)show me en garde.
(Barry:)Good. Knees bent,
slightly over the toe.
Non-sword hand up for balance.
(groans) I am going
to feel this tomorrow.
(Barry:)The first move
is called an advance.
You move your front foot
forward, heel to toe.
(Barry:)Back foot
follows.
So front foot forward,
heel to toe.
Back foot follows.
Now you try. Advance.
(Barry:)And advance.
And advance.
(Leonard:)This is easy.
I didn't need to wear a cup.
KRIPKE:
Good.
(Barry:)The next move is called
a retreat.
(Barry:)Step back.
(Barry:)Back foot first, toe to heel.
Front foot follows.
(Sheldon:)On three.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me, Barry?
Yes.
(Sheldon:)When can I stab
one of my friends?
(Barry:)In fencing,
we don't call it a stab.
(Barry:)We call it a touch.
Uh, yes, I'm aware.
(Sheldon:)But if I say I want
to touch one of my friends,